{
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "What is jQuery?",
      "answer": "Dynamically inserting, updating or removing HTML.  Registering click or other change events. Animating HTML elements. Download data from databases."
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "jQuery is JavaScript library or JSON library?",
      "answer": "JavaScript library."
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "What scripting language is jQuery written in?",
      "answer": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "Which sign does jQuery use as a shortcut for jQuery?",
      "answer": "$ sign"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Is jQuery a library for client scripting or server scripting?",
      "answer": "Client scripting."
    },
   {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "What is CDN?",
      "answer": "Content Delivery Network (CDN) is a system of computers that exist all over the world and cache files for users to access. CDNs can greatly reduce the load time of a page by offering files at a higher bandwidth from a server that is physically closer to your visitor than your web server might be."
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "What does this code represent for? <script   src='https://code.jquery.com/jquery-3.3.1.min.js'   integrity='sha256-FgpCb/KJQlLNfOu91ta32o/NMZxltwRo8QtmkMRdAu8='   crossorigin='anonymous'></script>",
      "answer": "jQuery CDN"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "Where do you place jQuery code?",
      "answer": "adding a line in between the opening (< head >) and closing (< /head >) HTML header tags."
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "Which jQuery function is used to prevent code from running, before the document is finished loading?",
      "answer": "$(document) .ready()"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "What jQuery method is used to insert content after a selected element?",
      "answer": "after()"
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "The jQuery DOM manipulation method that returns or declares text content for selected elements is",
      "answer": "text()"
    },
   {
      "id": "12",
      "question": "What jQuery method is used to identify attribute values?",
      "answer": "attr()"
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "What type of jQuery selector can be used to identify elements that make use of a specific class?",
      "answer": "Class Selector"
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "What type of jQuery selector can be used to identify elements that make use of a specific class?",
      "answer": "document .ready()"
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "What is the name of the jQuery element that allows you to select and manipulate HTML objects?",
      "answer": "Selectors"
    }
  ]
}